Can she hear us?
OK, great.
Can we call her Mina?
[Speaker 2] OK.
[Speaker 1] Then
let's get started.
The first question is, why does
she have to hide her identity?
[Speaker 2] I don't show
my face because I don't
want people to recognize me.
It's too risky.
The consequences
could be terrible.
I'd also be putting my
whole family in danger.
talk openly about politics.
If you say something the
authorities don't like,
you're in serious trouble.
I don't want to
reveal my identity.
by the Iranian dictatorship.
Even prison hasn't stopped
them from speaking out.
Narges Mohammadi was detained
for defending human rights.
She managed to send
us this letter.
(NON-ENGLISH SPEECH)
We've seen grainy video
of her on some security
camera collapsing in some
sort of holding room.
The people of
Iran took the risk
of filming these
videos themselves,
so that the entire world
could see what was happening.
We heard their clamor for we've
all experienced a revolution
in our own histories.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
I felt like I'd lost
a family member.
What if it'd be me?
And supposing it had
happened to someone close
to me, what would
have happened?
We were extremely sad until
the demonstration started,
and people began to protest.
gave us strength and hope.
a spontaneous demonstration.
For the first time, women
were leading the protest.